[Music]
I
never only come with
intentions take
[Music]
me I give you my loing and
I give you roll at
a you come alone with
conventions oh baby
[Music]
a sometimes we
get sometimes we can't
over what these old
I never you the
time I never tell you that I
won give you my loing and the face
you only
me you com with
intention dve me and
me I never tell you the
time I never tell you that I W
I'm talking to
you
[Music]
talking oh blood CL Come Again Come
Again boy we don't want to off
that's anyway we stop
make
[Music]
me don't blame
it don't blame for the way you feel
because you know that my love is real
and you're my heart that you come to
steal oh
cuz I'm just a regular guy and I'm going
to tell you
why don't hurt me
baby don't me make song on because
[Music]
this you child from the
every day make I tell you what I
say got a lovers
play don't let love slip
away
[Music]
uh-uh who you to tell me that I'm wrong
but this one have to carry on and
and show you who you are
[Music]
[Applause]
up your
arm because my love Bo you girl is war
[Music]
oh all
right it's like a in my
brain I circulate through my
[Music]
vein
yes stop it
[Music]